Register of the Fritz Machlup Papers, 1911-1983
Hoover Institution Archives
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1947-1974.
  - See photo card catalog (Photo-file Photo file)